

#### ABOUT

A committed individual with an interest in technology and problemsolving. With two years of experience in IT support and a CCNA certificate, My goal is to ensure seamless operations and user satisfaction.

I'm also a 3D modeler specializing in hard surface modeling using Blender software. With four years of experience, I've worked on various projects ranging from product design to art gallery design. Please don't hesitate to reach out to me with any questions or concerns you may have.

#### SKILLS

Certificate: CCNA

Design: Blender, Photoshop

Azerbaijani: Native Speaker

**English:** Proficient

WEBSITE

behance.net/mahirasadli

CONTACT



in



HIRE

fiverr.

# MAHIR ASADLI

Baku, Azerbaijan Mobile: +994507961987

E-mail: mahiresedli@proton.me

## Experience

Accounting Assistant, Gemiqaya LTD, (Jan 2008 – Jun 2011, Nakhchivan)

As an Accounting Assistant. I was using Microsoft Excel to do basic bookkeeping and accounting tasks in construction company.

Gemigaya Autoservice, (Dec 2013 – May 2015, Nakhchivan)

As a Purchasing Agent. I was in charge of finding products in local markets for the company.

Cahan Holding, (Apr 2014 – May 2014, Nakhchivan)

As a Purchasing Assistan. I was in charge of finding products in local markets for the company

Web Content Manager (Aug. 2014 – Apr 2020, Baku)

As a Web Content Manager. My job was to coordinate the site content.

3D Designer, (May 2020 - May 2024)

Product Modeler. Hard Surface modeling, Varius animations and Art Gallery Interior Designer

## **Education**

CompTIA A+ Core 1 and Core2 (Apr, 2024, Baku)

Cisco Certified Network Associate Routing and Switching ( Aug, 2015, Baku)

NDU International Relations and Foreign Languages, Bachelor degree (Sep 2005 – May 2009, Nakhchivan)

# Help Desk Skills:

- ✓ IT knowledge
- ✓ Customer service
- ✓ Technical troubleshooting
- ✓ Problem-solving
- ✓ Teamwork

## **Blender Skills:**

- ✓ Animation
- ✓ Hard Surface Modeling
- ✓ Texturing
- ✓ Rendering